[{
    "questionNumber": 1,
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "HIP PRINCIPLE",
    "correctAnswer": "Prince Philip",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "CHILL COALMINES",
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Collins",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "LUGN SMÖRIG ALBERT",
    "correctAnswer": "Gunilla Bergström",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "IRENA",
    "correctAnswer": "Einár",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "KARLS LIVS",
    "correctAnswer": "Lars Vilks",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "WOOLLEN CLIP",
    "correctAnswer": "Colin Powell",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "MORDFALLENS UDD",
    "correctAnswer": "Donald Rumsfeld",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "CARINS HÖGRA ZONS",
    "correctAnswer": "Göran Zachrisson",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "RICH CULT-MISQUOTER",
    "correctAnswer": "Curt-Eric Holmquist",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "STORHETENS SNUVA",
    "correctAnswer": "Svante Thuresson",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "LANSEN ROR",
    "correctAnswer": "Lars Norén",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "RIV ANSGARS MIDJA",
    "correctAnswer": "Sigvard Marjasin",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "DONUTS MUTED",
    "correctAnswer": "Desmond Tutu",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "MYNTENS MOTDRAG",
    "correctAnswer": "Tommy Engstrand",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  }
]

